{
    "subject": "resource/Stone_Poneys",
    "predicate": "property/pastMembers",
    "object": "Shep Cooke",
    "human_readable": "Shep Cooke was a past member of Stone Poneys.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.984548032283783,
            "question": "When was Shep Cooke a member of Stone Poneys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9689754843711853,
            "question": "Was Shep Cooke part of Stone Poneys in the present day?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106781482696533,
            "question": "What impact did Shep Cooke have on Stone Poneys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8987112641334534,
            "question": "Is there any information about Shep Cooke's career outside of Stone Poneys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7077968716621399,
            "question": "Who was Shep Cooke?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6705675721168518,
            "question": "What band was Shep Cooke a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5342116951942444,
            "question": "Can you name other musicians who were in Stone Poneys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5253117680549622,
            "question": "Where was Stone Poneys based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3786063492298126,
            "question": "What kind of music did Stone Poneys play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33737674355506897,
            "question": "Were there any famous songs by Stone Poneys?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shep Cooke was a past member of Stone Poneys.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4337_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of music did Stone Poneys play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4337_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Stone Poneys based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4337_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other musicians who were in Stone Poneys?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4337_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4337_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Shep Cooke was a member of the Stone Poneys, which supports the statement that he was a past member of this band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}